http://www.indsci.com/en/privacy-statement/

1.0   What this policy covers
Your privacy is important to us, and so is being transparent about how we collect, use, and share information about you. This policy is intended to help you understand:
1.1   What information we collect about you - Section 2.0
1.2   How we use information we collect - Section 3.0
1.3   What happens if you do not provide us with the information we request or ask that we stop processing your information? - Section 4.0
1.4   How we share information we collect - Section 5.0
1.5   How we store and secure information we collect - Section 6.0
1.6   How to access and control your information - Section 7.0
1.7   How we transfer information we collect internationally - Section 8.0
1.8   Privacy Shield Notice - Section 9.0
1.9   Other important privacy information - Section 10.0
This Privacy Policy covers the information we collect about you when you use our products or services, or otherwise interact with us (for example, by attending our events), unless a different policy is displayed.  This privacy statement describes how Industrial Scientific Corporation and its subsidiaries, including but not limited to, Predictive Solutions Corporation (collectively, "Industrial Scientific") collect and use the personal information you provide.  Industrial Scientific is headquartered at 1 Life Way, Pittsburgh, PA 15205 in the United States.  We offer a wide range of products, including but not limited to our iNet, SafetyNet and SmartWork platforms and Industrial Scientific gas monitor and connected-device products.  We refer to all of these products, together with our other services and websites as "Services" in this policy.
This policy also explains your choices about how we use information about you.  Your choices include how you can object to certain uses of information about you and how you can access and update certain information about you.
If you do not agree with this policy, do not access or use our Services or interact with any other aspect of our business.
Where we provide the Services under contract with an organization (for example your employer) that organization controls the information processed by the Services. For more information, please see Notice to End Users below.
If you are a resident of the State of California in the United States of America and your personal information is governed by the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), please see our CCPA Privacy Notice for more information on how we handle your personal data.
2.0   What information we collect about you
We collect information about you when you provide it to us, when you use our Services, and when other sources provide it to us, as further described below.
2.1   Information you provide to us
We collect information about you when you input it into the Services or otherwise provide it directly to us.
2.1.1   Account and Profile Information: We collect information about you when you register for an account, create or modify your profile, set preferences, sign-up for or make purchases through the Services. For example, you provide your contact information and, in some cases, billing information when you register for the Services. You also have the option of adding a display name, profile photo, job title, and other details to your profile information to be displayed in our Services.  We keep track of your preferences when you select settings within the Services.
2.1.2   Content you provide through our products: The Services include the Industrial Scientific products you use, where we collect and store content that you post, send, receive and share. This content includes any information about you that you or your employer may choose to include (e.g. files and links uploaded to the Services). Examples of content we collect and store include:
Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, company name
Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password and employee id
Birth date for recordable safety incidents
Any feedback you provide to us
Content also includes the files and links you upload to the Services.
2.1.3   Content you provide through our websites: The Services also include our websites owned or operated by us. We collect other content that you submit to these websites, which include social media or social networking websites operated by us. For example, you provide content to us when you provide feedback or when you participate in any interactive features, surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, activities or events.
2.1.4   Information you provide through our support channels: The Services also include our customer support, where you may choose to submit information regarding a problem you are experiencing with a Service.  Whether you designate yourself as a technical contact, open a support ticket, speak to one of our representatives directly or otherwise engage with our support team, you will be asked to provide contact information, a summary of the problem you are experiencing, and any other documentation, screenshots or information that would be helpful in resolving the issue.
2.1.5   Payment Information:  We collect certain payment and billing information when you register for certain paid Services.  For example, we ask you to designate a billing representative, including name and contact information, upon registration.  You might also provide payment information, such as payment card details, which we collect via secure payment processing services.
2.2   Information we collect automatically when you use the Services
We collect information about you when you use our Services, including browsing our websites and taking certain actions within the Services.
2.2.1   Your use of the Services: We keep track of certain information about you when you visit and interact with any of our Services. This information includes the features you use; the links you click on; the type, size and filenames of attachments you upload to the Services; frequently used search terms; and how you interact with others on the Services.  We also collect information about the teams and people you work with to provide Services that may improve safety within your work environment.
2.2.2   Device and Connection Information: We collect information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Services. This device information includes your connection type and settings when you install, access, update, or use our Services. We also collect information through your device about your operating system, browser type, IP address, URLs of referring/exit pages, device identifiers, and crash data. We use your IP address and/or country preference in order to approximate your location to provide you with a better Service experience.  How much of this information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services.
2.2.3   Location information: When you download and use our mobile applications, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location in order to determine your device location for safety purposes. If you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth above, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application.
2.2.4   Mobile device information: We also may send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about events. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information. We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from.
2.2.5   Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: Industrial Scientific and our third-party partners, such as our advertising and analytics partners, use cookies and other tracking technologies (e.g., web beacons, device identifiers and pixels) to provide functionality and to recognize you across different Services and devices. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising  click here or if located in the European Union click here.
2.3   Information we receive from other sources
We receive information about you from other Service users, from third-party services, from our related companies, and from our business and channel partners.
2.3.1   Other users of the Services: Other users of our Services may provide information about you when they submit content through the Services.  For example, you may be mentioned in a SafetyNet observation opened by someone else.  We also receive your email address from other Service users (such as your employer) when they provide it in order to invite you to the Services.  Similarly, an administrator may provide your contact information when they designate you as the billing or technical contact on your company's account.
2.3.2   Other services you link to your account: We receive information about you when you or your administrator integrate or link a third-party service with our Services.  For example, if you create an account or log into the Services using your company’s single sign-on product, we receive your name and email address to authenticate you.
2.3.3   Fortive Companies:  We receive information about you from companies that are owned or operated by our parent company, Fortive, in accordance with their terms and policies.  For example, Industrial Scientific rents Fluke instruments and Fluke is a Fortive operating company.
2.3.4   Industrial Scientific Partners:  We work with a global network of partners who provide consulting, implementation, training and other services around our products.  Some of these partners also help us to market and promote our products, generate leads for us, and resell our products.  We receive information from these partners, such as billing information, billing and technical contact information, company name, what Industrial Scientific products you have purchased or may be interested in, evaluation information you have provided, what events you have attended, and what country you are in.
2.3.5   Other Partners: We receive information about you and your activities on and off the Services from third-party partners, such as advertising and market research partners who provide us with information about your interest in and engagement with, our Services and online advertisements.
3.0   How we use information we collect
How we use the information we collect depends in part on which Services you use, how you use them, and any preferences you have communicated to us.  Below are the specific purposes for which we use the information we collect about you.
3.1.1   To provide the Services and personalize your experience:
We use information about you to provide the Services to you, including to process transactions with you, authenticate you when you log in, provide customer support, and operate and maintain the Services.  For example, we use the name and picture you provide in your account to identify you to other Service users. Our Services also include tailored features that personalize your experience, enhance your productivity, and improve your ability to collaborate effectively with others. Where you use multiple Services, we combine information about you and your activities to provide an integrated experience, such as to allow you to find information from one Service while searching from another or to present relevant product information as you travel across our websites.
3.1.2   For research and development:  We are always looking for ways to make our Services smarter, faster, secure, integrated, and useful to you.  We use collective learnings about how people use our Services and feedback provided directly to us to troubleshoot and to identify trends, usage, activity patterns and areas for integration and improvement of the Services.  We also test and analyze certain new features with some users before rolling the feature out to all users.
3.1.3   To communicate with you about the Services: We use your contact information to send transactional communications via email and within the Services, including confirming your purchases, reminding you of subscription expirations, responding to your comments, questions and requests, providing customer support, and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and administrative messages.  We provide tailored communications based on your activity and interactions with us.  We also send you communications as you onboard to a particular Service to help you become more proficient in using that Service.  These communications are part of the Services and in most cases, you cannot opt out of them.  If an opt out is available, you will find that option within the communication itself or in your account settings.
3.1.4   To market, promote and drive engagement with the Services:
We use your contact information and information about how you use the Services to send promotional communications that may be of specific interest to you, including by email and by displaying Industrial Scientific ads on other companies' websites and applications, as well as on platforms like Facebook and Google.  These communications are aimed at driving engagement and maximizing what you get out of the Services, including information about new features, survey requests, newsletters, and events we think may be of interest to you.  We also communicate with you about new product offers, promotions and contests.  You can control whether you receive these communications as described below under "Opt-out of communications."
3.1.5   Customer support: We use your information to resolve technical issues you encounter, to respond to your requests for assistance, to analyze crash information, and to repair and improve the Services.
3.1.6   For safety and security: We use information about you and your Service use to verify accounts and activity, to monitor suspicious or fraudulent activity and to identify violations of Service policies.
3.1.7   To protect our legitimate business interests and legal rights:
Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, interests and the interests of others, we use information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory, and audit functions, and disclosures in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business.
3.1.8   With your consent: We use information about you where you have given us consent to do so for a specific purpose not listed above.  For example, we may publish testimonials or featured customer stories to promote the Services, with your permission.
3.1.9   Legal bases for processing (for EEA users):
If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws.  The legal bases depend on the Services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:
We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Services;
Where this is necessary for the performance of a contract with you for the provision of our Services or to take steps at your request prior to entering into such contract;
To comply with our legal obligations, for example to keep records and accounts, or to carry out identity checks and other verifications prescribed by law;
It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and interests; or
You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose, for instance to send you promotional communications related to our Services.
If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place.  Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.
4.0   What happens if you do not provide us with the information we request or ask that we stop processing your information?
Where we need to collect personal data in order to enter into or perform a contract and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to enter into or perform that contract, but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.
When you use our Services, for instance our mobile applications, tools and devices, you may be asked to provide certain information. Where you do not do so, and that Service, or certain features of the Service, requires this information, the Service or certain features of the Service will no longer function.
4.1   Do we make automated decisions concerning you?
Our services use an automated decision-making system to identify potentially hazardous conditions in the environment in connection with identity and location information of a data subject.
You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which has legal consequences for you or similarly significant effects. While we’re confident that the technology works, we understand that not everyone is comfortable with decisions being left entirely up to machines. If you have any questions about our identity checking system, please contact us on using the details at the end of this Privacy Statement.
4.2   Do we use Cookies to collect personal data on you?
Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as web beacons) are used to enhance your experience by allowing us to tailor our content based on your interests and distinguish you from other users of our Services.
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your device. A cookie can contain information, such as a user ID or preferences, which we use to personalize content, track the pages you've visited or to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our website or use our Services.
We use the following types of cookies:
Strictly Necessary Cookies. These are cookies or other tracking mechanisms necessary to make our Services function as intended. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to use a shopping cart.
Analytical/Performance Cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our Services. This helps us to improve the way our Services work, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
Functionality Cookies. These cookies enable us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region). They may also be used to recognize you when you return to our Services.
Third-Party and Marketing Cookies: We may allow third parties to place cookies on your device for advertising and analytics purposes. For more information about these cookies, please see above.
Where required by law, we will ask you for your consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our Services. You will be presented with a choice of cookies for which we need to ask for your consent and a description of what function these cookies perform. If you agree to cookies, we will place a cookie on your device. If you change your mind, simply delete the cookies on your device (please see: https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/) and you will be asked again if you agree or disagree with our use of cookies when you next visit our Services.
You can also adjust your browser settings to receive a message every time a cookie is installed on your computer or to prevent their installation altogether. Although rejection of cookies will not interfere with your ability to interact with most of our Services, you will need to accept cookies if you choose to areas access portions of our Services that require registration or login. Certain other functions and/or services might be unavailable to you if you reject cookies altogether (such as remembering your choice of language on a website).
4.3   What about marketing?
We would like to be able to contact you from time to time about our new similar products and services and promotional offers, where we have your permission or are otherwise permitted by applicable law to do so.
5.0   How we share information we collect
We make safety and equipment management tools, and we want them to work well for you.  This means sharing information through the Services and with certain third parties.  We share information we collect about you in the ways discussed below, including in connection with possible business transfers, but we are not in the business of selling information about you to advertisers or other third parties.
5.1   Sharing with other Service users
When you use the Services, we share certain information about you with other Service users.
5.1.1   For collaboration: You can create content, which may contain information about you, and grant permission to others to see, share, edit, copy and download that content based on settings you or your administrator (if applicable) select.  Some of the collaboration features of the Services display some or all of your profile information to other Service users when you share or interact with specific content.
5.1.2   Managed accounts and administrators: If you register or access the Services using an email address with a domain that is owned by your employer or organization, and such organization wishes to establish an account or site, certain information about you including your name, profile picture, contact info, content and past use of your account may become accessible to that organization’s administrator and other Service users sharing the same domain.  If you are an administrator for a particular site or group of users within the Services, we may share your contact information with current or past Service users, for the purpose of facilitating Service-related requests.
5.2   Sharing with third parties
We share information with third parties that help us operate, provide, improve, integrate, customize, support and market our Services.
5.2.1   Service Providers: We work with third-party service providers to provide website and application development, hosting, maintenance, backup, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, analysis and other services for us, which may require them to access or use information about you.  If a service provider needs to access information about you to perform services on our behalf, they do so under close instruction from us, including policies and procedures designed to protect your information.
5.2.2   Industrial Scientific Partners: We work with third parties who provide consulting, sales, and technical services to deliver and implement customer solutions around the Services. We may share your information with these third parties in connection with their services, such as to assist with billing and collections and to provide localized support, and to provide customizations.  We may also share information with these third parties where you have agreed to that sharing.
5.2.3   Third Party Apps: You, your administrator or other Service users may choose to add new functionality or change the behavior of the Services by installing third party apps within the Services.  Doing so may give third-party apps access to your account and information about you like your name and email address, and any content you choose to use in connection with those apps.  Third-party app policies and procedures are not controlled by us, and this privacy policy does not cover how third-party apps use your information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of third parties before connecting to or using their applications or services to learn more about their privacy and information handling practices. If you object to information about you being shared with these third parties, please uninstall the app.
5.2.4   Links to Third-Party Sites: The Services may include links that direct you to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit information to any of those third-party sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies, not this one. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.
5.2.5   Social Media Widgets: The Services may include links that direct you to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Your use of and any information you submit to any of those third-party sites is governed by their privacy policies, not this one.
5.2.6   Third-Party Widgets: Some of our Services contain widgets and social media features, such as the Twitter "tweet" button. These widgets and features collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Widgets and social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
5.2.7   With your consent: We share information about you with third parties when you give us consent to do so.  For example, we often display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our public websites. With your consent, we may post your name alongside the testimonial.
5.2.8   Compliance with Enforcement Requests and Applicable Laws; Enforcement of Our Rights:
In exceptional circumstances, we may share information about you with a third party if we believe that sharing is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements, (b) enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) protect the security or integrity of our products and services, (d) protect Industrial Scientific, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person.
5.3   Sharing with affiliated companies
We share information we collect with affiliated companies and, in some cases, with prospective affiliates.  Affiliated companies are companies owned or operated by us.  The protections of this privacy policy apply to the information we share in these circumstances.
5.3.1   Fortive companies: We share information we have about you with other Fortive corporate affiliates in order to operate and improve products and services and to offer other Fortive affiliated services to you. This includes companies listed here.
5.3.2   Business Transfers: We may share or transfer information we collect under this privacy policy in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Services if a transaction takes place, as well as any choices you may have regarding your information.
6.0   How we store and secure information we collect
6.1   Information storage and security
We use data hosting service providers in the United States to host the information we collect, and we use technical measures to secure your data.
While we implement safeguards designed to protect your information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that data, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, is absolutely safe from intrusion by others.
If you use our docking station server Services, responsibility for securing storage and access to the information you put into the Services rests with you and not Industrial Scientific. We strongly recommend that docking station server users configure SSL to prevent interception of data transmitted over networks and to restrict access to the databases and other storage points used.
6.2   How long we keep information
How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below.  After such time, we will either delete your information or, if this is not possible (for example, because the information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.
6.2.1   Account information: We retain your account information for as long as your account is active and a reasonable period thereafter in case you decide to re-activate the Services.  We also retain some of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements, to support business operations, and to continue to develop and improve our Services. Where we retain information for Service improvement and development, we take steps to eliminate information that directly identifies you, and we only use the information to uncover collective insights about the use of our Services, not to specifically analyze personal characteristics about you.
6.2.2   Information you share on the Services: If your account is deactivated or disabled, some of your information and the content you have provided will remain in order to allow your team members or other users to make full use of the Services.  For example, we continue to display messages you sent to the users that received them and continue to display content you provided.
6.2.3   Managed accounts: If the Services are made available to you through an organization (e.g., your employer), we retain your information as long as required by the administrator of your account.  For more information, see "Managed accounts and administrators" above.
6.2.4   Marketing information: If you have elected to receive marketing emails from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our Services, such as when you last opened an email from us or ceased using your Industrial Scientific account.  We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.
7.0   How to access and control your information
By law, you have a number of rights when it comes to your personal data, and we have summarized these below. Further information and advice about your rights can be obtained from the data protection regulator in your country. Where the Services are administered for you by an administrator (see "Notice to End Users" below), you may need to contact your administrator to assist with your requests first.  For all other requests, you may contact us as provided in the Contact Us section below to request assistance.
7.1.1   The right to be informed:  You have the right to be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how we use your information and your rights. This is why we’re providing you with the information in this Privacy Statement.
7.1.2   The right of access:  You have the right to obtain access to your information (if we’re processing it), and certain other information (similar to that provided in this Privacy Statement). This is so you’re aware and can check that we’re using your information in accordance with data protection law.
7.1.3   The right to rectification:  You are entitled to have your information corrected if it’s inaccurate or incomplete.
7.1.4   The right to erasure:  This is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’ and, in simple terms, enables you to request the deletion or removal of your information where there’s no compelling reason for us to keep using it. This is not a general right to erasure; there are exceptions.
7.1.5   The right to restrict processing:      You have rights to ‘block’ or suppress further use of your information. When processing is restricted, we can still store your information, but may not use it further. We keep lists of people who have asked for further use of their information to be ‘blocked’ to make sure the restriction is respected in future.
7.1.6   The right to data portability:  You have rights to obtain and reuse your personal data for your own purposes across different services. For example, if you decide to switch to a new provider, this enables you to move, copy or transfer your information easily between our IT systems and theirs safely and securely, without affecting its usability.
7.1.7   The right to object to processing:  You have the right to object to certain types of processing, including processing based on our legitimate interests and processing for direct marketing (i.e. if you no longer want to be contacted with potential opportunities).
7.1.8   The right to lodge a complaint:  You have the right to lodge a complaint about the way we handle or process your personal data with your national data protection regulator.
7.1.9   The right to withdraw consent:  If you have given your consent to anything we do with your personal data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time (although if you do so, it does not mean that anything we have done with your personal data with your consent up to that point is unlawful). This includes your right to withdraw consent to us using your personal data for marketing purposes.
You may be able to opt out of receiving personalized advertisements from other companies who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or who subscribe to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit: http://www.aboutads.info/, http://optout.networkadvertising.org/ and http://www.youronlinechoices.eu.
7.1.10   Send "Do Not Track" Signals: Some browsers have incorporated "Do Not Track" (DNT) features that can send a signal to the websites you visit indicating you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, our Services do not currently respond to browser DNT signals. You can use the range of other tools we provide to control data collection and use, including the ability to opt out of receiving marketing from us as described above.
7.1.11   Data portability: Data portability is the ability to obtain some of your information in a format you can move from one service provider to another (for instance, when you transfer your mobile phone number to another carrier).  Depending on the context, this applies to some of your information, but not to all of your information.  Should you request it, we will provide you with an electronic file of your basic account information and the information you create on the spaces under your sole control.
8.0   How we transfer information we collect internationally
8.1   International transfers of information we collect
We collect information globally and primarily store that information in the United States. We transfer, process and store your information outside of your country of residence, to wherever we or our third-party service providers operate for the purpose of providing you the Services.  Whenever we transfer your information, we take steps to protect it.
8.1.1   International transfers within the Fortive Companies: To facilitate our global operations, we transfer information to the United States and allow access to that information from countries in which the Fortive owned or operated companies have operations for the purposes described in this policy. These countries may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the laws of many of the countries where our customers and users are based. When we share information about you within and among Fortive corporate affiliates, we rely on the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework to safeguard the transfer of information we collect from the European Economic Area. Please see our Privacy Shield notice below for more information or contact us as provided below.
8.1.2   International transfers to third parties: Some of the third parties described in this privacy policy, which provide services to us under contract, are based in other countries that may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the country in which you reside. When we share information of customers in the European Economic Area, we make use of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework or other appropriate legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer. Please see our Privacy Shield Notice below.
9.0   Privacy Shield Notice
[Industrial Scientific Corporation is aware of the European Court of Justice’s July 16, 2020 ruling invalidating the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.  While awaiting new guidance from international data protection authorities, ISC will continue to follow the principles underlying the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and monitor compliance changes in the countries where we serve customers.]
Industrial Scientific Corporation and its U.S. subsidiaries (Predictive Solutions Corporation) complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (Privacy Shield) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom to the United States in reliance on Privacy Shield. Industrial Scientific Corporation has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such information. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy statement and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit http://www.privacyshield.gov.
In the context of onward transfers, we maintain responsibility for the processing of personal information we receive under the Privacy Shield and transfer to third party agents acting on our behalf.  We assume liability under the Privacy Shield principles if the third-party agent processes such personal information in a manner that is inconsistent with the Principles, unless we prove that we were not responsible for the event giving rise to the damages.
We encourage you to contact us as provided below should you have a Privacy Shield-related (or general privacy-related) complaint.  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.  Through this third-party dispute resolution provider, we have also committed to cooperating and complying with the information and advice provided by an informal panel of data protection authorities in the European Economic Area (as applicable) in relation to unresolved complaints (as further described in the Privacy Shield Principles). You may also contact your local data protection authority within the European Economic Area (as applicable) for unresolved complaints.
Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, including when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted, you may invoke binding arbitration.
We are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).
10.0   Other important privacy information
10.1   Notice to End Users
Many of our products are intended for use by organizations. Where the Services are made available to you through an organization (e.g. your employer), that organization is the administrator of the Services and is responsible for the accounts and/or Service sites over which it has control. If this is the case, please direct your data privacy questions to your administrator, as your use of the Services is subject to that organization's policies. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of an administrator's organization, which may be different than this policy.
Administrators are able to:
require you to reset your account password;
restrict, suspend or terminate your access to the Services;
access information in and about your account;
access or retain information stored as part of your account;
install or uninstall third-party apps or other integrations
In some cases, administrators can also:
restrict, suspend or terminate your account access;
change the email address associated with your account;
change your information, including profile information;
restrict your ability to edit, restrict, modify or delete information
Even if the Services are not currently administered to you by an organization, if you use an email address provided by an organization (such as your work email address) to access the Services, then the owner of the domain associated with your email address (e.g. your employer) may assert administrative control over your account and use of the Services at a later date.  Once an administrator asserts control over your account or use of the Services, you will no longer be able to change the email address associated with your account without administrator approval.
Please contact your organization or refer to your administrator’s organizational policies for more information.
10.2   Our policy towards children
The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16. If we become aware that a child under the age of 16 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact our support services.
10.3   Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by adding a notice on the Services homepages, login screens, or by sending you an email notification. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.
If you disagree with any changes to this privacy policy, you will need to stop using the Services and deactivate your account(s), as outlined above.
10.4   Contact Us
If you have questions on the processing of your personal data, would like to exercise any of your rights, or are unhappy with how we’ve handled your information, please direct your inquiry to the Data Privacy Office at Industrial Scientific Corporation, which we have appointed to be responsible for facilitating such inquiries. The details of the data protection officers that we have appointed can be found here.
Home |
Contact Us |
Where to Buy |
Product Search |
Quote Cart |
Terms of Use |
Privacy Statement |
Login
© Industrial Scientific  |  One Life Way Pittsburgh, PA 15205-7500 USA  |  +1 412-788-4353  |  info@indsci.com
